Now we'll introduce
you those who will play flipping tiles!
GWSN - Girls in the Park Translations
Subtitles by archie
A great warrior who
only protects Minju
(Reciting poetry)
Kim Seokyeong, who has
memorized poetry in Seodang
for 10 years.
(Reciting poetry)
Wishing to be an Emperor
instead of an Empress,
I'm the ambitious Minju.
Yes, I will someday embrace this country.
I like the things that are inanimate:
Lady Anne has been under
warrior Lena's protection
for years
The moon...
the stars...
flowers...
trees... (Groo)
Things like these...?
Warrior Lena, who has been practicing
martial arts since he was 5
After 15 years practicing martial arts,
I will protect our young lady!
M'lady!
I liked it so much I bought it~
Shopperholic Fairy
Princess Seoryeong
Since I bought this headband yesterday and this skirt today,
should I buy a hairpin tomorrow?
Great!
Wait a minute...
Where is our house...?
Hello. It's Girls in the Park's Lena.
Today we will play a game of tile flipping.
It is played on the New Year's Day, in the national festival.
Ah, really?
Then, how are the teams split?
Uh, it looks like we are dressed in pairs.
How about using it?
Looks good!~
Take position!
So we'll introduce ourselves from there.
We are the siblings who are the best players in Seodang.
[Seoryoung] I'm his sister.
[A lady shedding tears]
M'lady, don't cry.
I'll take care of everything that makes my lady cry.
[Sharp fighting skills for the lady!]
(Not yet decided their roles.)
Focus on the brainstorming over there.
Character #1!
Yeah!
Character number 1?
Don't bother me!
[Minju] I hope you don't glare at me!
[Anne] Whatever...
Alright!
Kim Moosa, take care of it!
Myself...
I love Minju!
Is that okay?
Well done!
Now that we've introduced the pairs,
the thing we're doing today...
What is it?
We will do a slap-match.
It must be fun~
Hey! Handle us the tile!
So, we are 3 teams
Let's pick the two teams that will compete first.
Let's~ do~ it!
So, the fairest way...
The national game!
I will take part!
Our representative is our lady.
Our master will do it.
As for us...
I'll let you do it.
Yes! Understood.
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Anne's team eliminated.]
[Miya won!]
This team will compete in the finals, then.
[Lena] Let's start with our teams.
[Seoryoung] Alright.
If you speak in a foreign language, you'll have to gesture your name with your butt!
Fine!
Let's make the tiles different writing on it.
Let's make our distinction.
I will draw my lady.
I drew her!
[Members felt like cringing.]
I will draw something very symbolic, not a picture.
We are the #1 group...
because we've ranked first in Seodang for 8 years.
Just because you won first place,...
you think you own the skies?
Our brother is a bit like that, but it's okay.
The rumors say you spent a lot of money?
Hey!
That's also a skill!
Let's start the game...
[Lena spoke in English!]
Ok, let's hit the tile...
Wait a minute!
Time out!
[Minju also spoke in English!]
Because she used a foreign language.
Did you say "Time out"?
You should do the same.
Let's start~
Warrior style.
[The tile didn't flip.]
The young lady strength is great~
I believe you will do better!
Shake that side as well.
[A girl whose power is not a joke.]
If she hits you, you will fly away!
You should listen to her carefully!
If I made a mistake, my sister would hit me all the time...
Poor head!
"Sister... I'm not stupid~"
Please keep this video a secret to our father.
Try again.
[Flipping failed!]
Alright, alright!
This is your team...
No.
Those eyes that look at us...
What do you see?
Is there someone else?
What is out there?
What is it that you see?
Everyone, please understand my sister.
Now, everyone pay attention!
Our sister is going to throw it.
Don't make me upset.
[Failed to flip!]
Now, go faster!
Do it quieter since you'll do it faster.
[Answer]
[An endless match...]
In the end we won't flip any tiles
and we will end up only introducing ourselves!
OK!
There's no label! hahaha
Now, let's change partners!
Our Lady! M'lady's energy!
Please, do it quicker than before.
FYI, I am not good at flipping tiles.
[A warrior who does not know how to play.]
[A neverending game even if you do it quickly!]
I was so nervous that my clothes got loose.
What are you doing?
I'm ashamed!
You can't do that here...
[It almost got flipped!?]
Brother! You can do it!
I can do it.
I can do it!
[A warrior influenced by an officer.]
[Tile hitting the air.]
[Seoryeong, who is not a great player!]
Seoryeong is even worse than me!
[Changing partners makes no difference!]
M'lady is upside...
Why are you poking her face like this?!
[The warrior laughs at the lady's reaction.]
I'll think of it as the last one.
♪ As it's the last~ ♪
[Song by Blackpink]
Do you know this song?
♪ As it's the last~ ♪
I don't know what song this is.
Your body is moving~
The peasants say this dance is fashionable.
[Unexpectedly, the code fits well with a warrior and an officer!]
["Seriously..."]
Throw it, quickly!
[Jumping as much as she can.]
[It flipped!!]
[Members are surprised by the unexpected situation.]
Is this the power of the "As it's the last~"?
Were you fooling around until now?
Fitting...
The sword...
[How was it...?]
Sharpen the sword!
Everything comes out in the end.
The first game was won by the Kim Satgat team.
Congratulations!
Now then, our lady in the finalist team?
The concubine, yes.
It's the concubine's team.
Is there no label in the tile?
It disappeared?
Here it is~
[Stunned officer.]
Where did you come from?
Now, face each other!
Greet!
[A psychological warfare first.]
I will win by my father's name.
I'll win by my son!
Have you ever had a son?
Yes, my dear son!
So let's start playing.
I guess this lady is angry~
[A concubine surprised by the power of the lady.]
A little less strength.
Elder brother.
Oh, he's been doing a lot.
Aren't you more tired than her?
Our brother throws tiles until late at night.
[The brother boasting quick hand movements.]
That's why he couldn't memorize Hanja characters.
So I studied and my brother got a tile and the two are sharing grades.
You're short because you don't sleep at night!
Be quiet! My father is also short!
Please protect our father's name.
Okay, brother, let's start.
Shouldn't you do "As it's the last time~" again?
♪ As it's the last... ♪
[The siblings listen well.]
[Dance failed this time.]
I think you should throw it well. Or maybe she will cut you...
Believe in me!
[Lack of faith on success.]
The sound was loud, I love you~
[Members who are frantic because the tiles overlap.]
I heard that you dance really well nowadays.
[An officer more physical than intellectual.]
Looks like you're good at this.
Brother, what is the reason you didn't
turn off the lights early last night?
Is it for doing this, and not for studying?
[An officer with an usual talent!]
Oh, this is fun!
What's up?
[The ability to throw when dancing!]
[Surprised by another flip!]
[Picks it up immediately.]
[Successful flip!]
[He was so surprised he fell.]
What is happening?
My darling~!!!
[Seoryoung] Isn't that your son?
[Lena] Wait! What...?
How are you two related?
I am confused!
[Unsolved mystery of the concubine team.]
[Lady Anne got so surprised she went in shock.]
My lady shouldn't hear that!
She became shocked by this scene...
I think our brother went dumb with the shock.
M'lady don't!
Okay, so the winner has been decided.
[The concubine team wins.]
I cannot believe it, but...
Congratulations!
Congratulations~
Unfortunately, there are no prizes!
Just accept our congratulations.
You can take it as you want.
Oh, yes, I have a wish.
What is it? I'll listen!
I'll take both men here!
Don't do it!
[The officer had a breakdown!]
Do you like that??
You have to get permission from my dad!
I must protect our lady.
Okay, should we go back...
to the positions from before?
We flipped some tiles, but the winner was the concubine team.
[SR] Congratulations to everyone.
[SK] I congratulate you!
[Winning team: Concubine team!]
It is because I gave birth to a son~
[Proud concubine]
I don't know what son we are talking about now.
I hope everyone who watches us playing...
will have a Happy New Year's Day~
I love you all.
Everyone says that this is popular...
100 years from now.
What is it?
This is the Korean heart.
Ah, are you referring to the heart of Korea?
Now, let's end with 'Happy New Year'!
Happy New Year!
Be happy~
Accept this Korean heart~