GWSN - Girls in the Park Translations
We play well even at home!
1, 2! Waiting for you!
Hello~ We are the Girls in the Park!
Today we're also bringing something we can play well at home.
Today's game...
Drum roll~
Korean Karaoke!
This way, we have to rewrite our songs
and sing them in Korean.
Since we'll have teams with 2 members,
we'll have 3 teams.
I want to pick fast!
Let's split this way (picking side by side!)
So, let's start the game?
I like it!
Let's do paper, scissors and stone, members!
Oh, cool.
Lena, I love you!
So, which part are you going to do?
The Park in the Night Parte 2: Seoryoung e Miya
The Park in the Night Parte 3: Anne and Seokyoung
The Park in the Night Parte 1: Minju and Lena
Root for us~
Music, please!
We did well, didn't we?!
Very good!
(Puzzle) Moon's team is going to start~
Yeah~
Music, please!
Alright~ we've reached our goal~
Let's joke in English!
[KangKangJu with a broken English]
[That was Minju]
So good!
We love it! We love it!
I like our songs in Korean so much~
The song was good!
So, we're gonna start "Pinky Star"
because it's small like a finger.
Music, please!
Now that we've sung all the songs,
Pinky Star team: 75 points!
Puzzle Moon team: 90 points!
Red-Sun team: 100 points!
That said, we won!
[Congratulating music]
Groo! Bye!~~
Bye bye!
We love you, Korean!~