GWSN - Girls in the Park Translations
We are currently shooting the music video for 'Like it Hot'.
It's been so long since I've filmed a music video.
I'm a little excited!
Fighting!
[Members making art!]
The picture you see in the back...
is a picture we drew yesterday for today's
shoot, for 7 hours nonstop.
Can you see it?
[Q. What is your impression of your biggest hair styling change ever for this album?]
I went and sat down to change my hair...
I only knew that the end would be purple.
As soon as I sat down, they cut my bangs!
So I was confused!
I was a little worried... but the members
said it looks good.
- Do I look good?
- [Nodding our heads.]
Thank you!
[Q. Do you have any secrets to take care of the "hime" cut?]
Uh... love and care!
It's been a long time since I've filmed
a music video... so I'm getting a little awkward.
I think there's a little bit of awkwardness
because it's been a while since I did it.
Look at this!
I got a watch!
Seoryoung did it!
I'll show you some magic!
I will remove this.
Wipes that can erase it in one shot!﻿
Such thing doesn't exist!
My hands are cold!﻿
[A magician who controls them both.]
Today we finished the first day of
shootings for the music video.
It's been too long since we've filmed
a music video.
To be honest, I think I couldn't sleep
because I was so excited.
That's right! Me neither!
Maybe it's because it's been a while...
I used to sleep a lot.
Since I'm with the members...
It's a little more fun and relaxing.
I think there are a lot of pretty scenes, so I'm looking forward to how it'll turn out.
It was really fun to draw that!
Would you like to see it? Our work!
- Actually, it's not really our work.
- That's right!
- The artist...
I'll keep it a secret!
If there's a story behind the MV someday,
you'll know everything.
They did it for me!
So, the first scene of the first day has been filmed.
We'll continue to work hard! Fighting!
Now, let's move on to the "old car team"!
[Moving to the "Old Car Team"!]
Hello! I'm Soso, back in a cool way!
I tried a cool concept this time.
Anne, Miya and I are filming in a cool car.
Fighting!
We'll start with Anne's scene and
Miya and I will talk for a bit.
Then we'll go back to filming this scene.
Everyone, I think you can look forward
to this music video a lot!
Anne is lip syncing alone, right now.
- That's right!
- Have you seen the car?
- That's the car.
- The car is awesome.
A car that shows up in a lot of cool music videos!
You know what I mean, right, everyone?
Anne, unnie!
I've called Anne.
It's like overseas here, right? But it's Pyeongtaek.
Wow, what a great location!﻿
The sun is up and the weather is very nice.
Natural light!
Right! I was about to say that!
Miya is doing it now! Shall we go watch?
You always get it right, folks!
There's a scene where I drive this car.
I wonder if I can drive it myself.
Let's do it!﻿
[Q. Did you get your Korean license for this scene?]
Oh right! I have a driver's license in Japan...
I didn't have a driver's license in Korea
yet, so I got one!
Now I can drive in Korea!﻿
The first car I drive in Korea! This one!
Isn't that awesome?
But this car is a bit unusual.
They're teaching me how to drive!
[Minju will show up as a photographer.]
Don't make me laugh!﻿
What did we just do?
We just filmed a scene in the hallway.
I lip synched with the camera.
I didn't look at the camera.
This time, we're going to watch the scene again.
So, Lena is the only one who needs to take it again.
- Am I the only one filming?
- I'm filming, too.
I'm excited!﻿
And this is where we are!
We'll film the group dance later.
Here it is!﻿
I think it's going to be a tough journey!
Let's do our best!
1, 2, 3... Fighting!﻿
Where have you seen this? This picture!
It looks a little different, but...
this is the key I drew on the 'The Keys' album!
I drew this design!
There's my drawing!
Now we are going to film our first group dance scene.
The points here are made up of only 'Black & White'!
So these are our clothes!
Like this, the outfits and the set are
matching in 'Black & White'!
Because it's the first time we're filming a dance I'm feeling a little better now,
hoping that no one gets hurt and that
I can do a good job.
Fighting!﻿
My wish is to make good use of the
points just as we practiced.
Let's work hard!
Fighting!
Please! Don't let anyone get hurt!
I just did the choreography.
The floor is more slippery than I thought!
We're getting used to it and we're going to work hard for the rest of the shoot,
please keep an eye on us!
[Checking the choreography details!]
[End of the first group dance scene.]
You've worked hard! Go! Go!
Group dance scene! It.. is.. over!
It is now 11:54!
I came in today at 7 A.M.!
My nose is getting red!
It's the nose that tells the weather.
Call me "nose", please!
Hello! This is "nose"!
My nose is red! It's my nose!
Cute!
It's too cold!﻿
Do you see the eye makeup?
How did you see this?
Tears!
Fighting!﻿
Yeah, everyone!
We've finally finished filming the music video
for GWSN's 5th album, "Like It Hot".
- Great job!
- Thank you for your hard work!
Our members have been preparing
hard for a long time.
We've worked hard filming this...please
stream "Like it Hot" a lot!
And I hope you love our song "Like It Hot" a lot!
We will keep working hard!
Thank you!
So far,
1, 2! Waiting for you!
We are Girls in the Park! Thank you!