This is a style that I prepared with ambition.
Right now...
only one eye has lens.
I got these new lenses for "I Can't Breathe" stages.
I bought it intending to use both, but...
I thought it'd be special if I only wore one.
Reflecting on other people's opinions, I'm using one lens today.
I will show you more new styles in the remaining performances.
It's too early for you to be surprised because it's so new.
We're going to challenge more styles in the future.
I came here today because of "I Can't Breathe"...
I also got my hair dyed.
Because both Lena and Miya unnie did new colors.
If Groos watch it, I think they'll like it.
Fighting!
Starting today, it's "I Can't Breathe".
Oh, I dyed it today.
B-side track version.
Lena B-side version.
Groo, we came here to do a "I Can't Breathe" performance.
I was more nervous than I thought.
I did my best to sing live, though.
I'll monitor it later to see if it went well.
There's a day difference between yesterday (Like it Hot) and today, it suddenly turned dark.
So I hope that Groos enjoy it!
I hope you show a lot of love for "I Can't Breathe" in the future.
Today's first broadcast was a success!
Bye!
Good morning, Groo!
What time is it now?
I went to the beauty saloon at 4 AM....
At 4 in the morning.
I'm awake now.
Today is the last broadcast.
The saloon threw a surprise party last night.
It was touching.
It's the last show, but the manager teased me for being a fool.
He can't help it.
Please watch today's stage.
I told you it was the last night of "Like it Hot" this week.
It's also the first and last night of "I Can't Breathe."
We're doing our first and last show of "I Can't Breathe" at Show Champion.
I have a point for today.
Our teacher put a heart here, like this.
So I'm gonna point to this when I'm crying or laughing.
Groo, I love you!
Please watch the last performance, okay?
See you later!
I can't turn my head.
It's a historical drama.
Your Highness!
I have sinned to death!
It's a snack box.
It's a snack set.
This one I really don't know!
Jelly and... Chocolate Oreo.
This is really tasty.
I ate this this morning.
What language is this?
Amazing.
- What country is this from?
- Wow, thank you!
- I like this.
- Pretzels?
- Let's eat it in the car.
- We'll share it in the car.
Thank you!
Groo, I'll be back after the last performance.
Bye!
[Seoryeong is husky for giving it all in the last broadcast]
The last night of "I Can't Breathe" is over...
It was something I've been waiting for, but it's a pity that time passed so quickly.
[Seoryeong is husky for giving it all in the last broadcast]
It was the last night, so I wanted to do well.
I'm sorry I don't have more opportunities to show you more.
I'm missing something else...
If there were more opportunities, I could show you a little bit more.
Still, I think I showed everything on stage, because I worked really hard.
Please enjoy this performance and look forward to the next schedules.
Thank you very much!
[TALKING ABOUT HAIRSTYLES FOR CHARACTERS IN MOVIES...]
I've been growing this hair for a year!
Let's go!