Painter team?
[Bright mood]
Yeah, our painter team~
Our jacket shooting is over!
Yes, we took pictures in the MV shooting site
for the jacket shooting!
In this photo album...
we used the same backgrounds as in the MV...
I believe the MV will focus more into the scenes.
You think so too?
Over there...
We filmed the music video there earlier,
but I also shot the jacket here.
The photos came out really nice because...
it is so colorful and the light was shining on it!
Listen! I watched it from behind the scenes!
Very beautiful!
It came out really pretty!
Seokyoung is looking cool,
but she was really cute, to be honest.
I just pretended to be cool!
But because of these dumplings...
It was so cute!
It's true!
Lena also completely changed her style...
her feeling has changed, but she's so pretty!
But honestly,
what kind of pose should I do with this styling?
It's still a little difficult.
We're getting used to it while filming today!
You were very good! What?!
Really?
Really, really good!
And now the other team is getting ready outside!
I'm really looking forward to it!
Everyone, are you curious?
We can see the car now...
I'll just say this!
Learn about it as you watch!
Let's move on to the next camera team!
One, two, three!
I'm doing a jacket shooting!
Isn't that cool?
The always cool Miya...
[Miya moving to the next scene!]
Now I changed into a black and white dress!
The first outfit was sporty~
Jogger pants and a crop top, dressed sporty.
We were a little more chic and cool,
and now we have a more moody feeling.
Being pretty...
cool...
charismatic...
I'll do it all!
I have to take individual pictures now,
and then a group photo shoot!
I'm waiting because I haven't finished filming.
Please pray for a good photo shoot, everyone!
Let's pray together, groos!