05/27/21 MCountdown
"Like it Hot" backstage
Hi!
05/27/21 MCountdown
"Like it Hot" backstage
We're here to film the first broadcast of
"Like it Hot" at MCountdown!
05/27/21 MCountdown
"Like it Hot" backstage
We're here to film the first broadcast of
"Like it Hot" at MCountdown!
We have a pre-recording today, so we have to hurry up and get ready and go on stage within an hour.
I'm nervous and excited! That's why I'm shaking!
Anyway, I'll do my best! Fighting!
These are the pearls that I put on during the music video.
Since it's our first broadcast today, we're putting it on again!
It's very cool! I think it goes well with the hair color!
[Members having debate]
It's a big difference... 1cm is 10mm!
No! I'm 164cm tall!
Then Anne is 165 cm tall!
So what if you're smaller?
- Mosquito?
- You don't want to admit it, so pretend you don't understand!
- I'll admit it!
- Hurry and say it to the camera!
I admit I'm short.
May 27, Miya!
- Miya unnie has good proportions, so she doesn't look short!
- Isn't it right?
As expected of Lena! Lena is kind to me!
I'm going to sing with my eye today!
Like this!
- Are you singing with heart today?
- I call you with my heart!
- Are you speaking from your heart?
- Can you hear me?
Yeah, I do! Only good people can hear you.
- Miya can't hear you.
- My part is over now!
I'm done!
Come on, let's slate!
Today's point!
Eyebrows!
I'm not really doing it.
Wait a second.
I'll put some tape on it!
This is how you place the mic.
What do you think? Perfect?
[Nodding]
Today's point!
Isn't that cool?
"Performer Miya" is gradually coming out.
I'll be on stage (soon)!
[Fairy leader taking pictures]
[Waiting for the ring]
Politeness for this promotion!
Etiquette!
I'll make my breath smell good so Seoryoung
can do that ad-lib well!
This way Seoryoung will be able to perform well!
Because I care more than you think.
I gave you a good tip earlier, now I'll tell you a secret!
Hidden in this pretty ring... Se-cret!
This is the secret when I wear those.
This is because the ring is too big
they fly off when performing on stage.
I made it a little thicker by sticking some tape!
In-ear tape plays a big role!
Today's tip is over!
I am getting rid of the swelling.
[A surprise gift from choreographers]
Please blow the candle!
One, two, three!
They threw a little party to congratulate
us on our comeback.
- Surprise party!
- Wow, amazing!
Incredible. We will work hard!
Thank you!
05/28/21 Music Bank
"Like it Hot" Performance
Hi!
05/28/21 Music Bank
"Like it Hot" Performance
Today...﻿
05/28/21 Music Bank
"Like it Hot" Performance
Today...﻿
Music Bank!
I'm MC (Min)Dung!
Today, I'm picking members to do some interviews.
I'm nervous because I don't know who I'm picking first!
I don't know who to go to...
Miya unnie!
The first one is Miya!
It's our second "Like it Hot" stage.
Q. It's been a while since you came to Music Bank, how do you feel?
Ok! Thank you!
[Persuading MC Dung by whining]
The feeling of going up on stage?
Sense? (am I right?)
Are you coming out (on stage)?
But today, I'm using a handheld microphone.
There are many moves that we use our hands.
If you do this the mic will squeak.
Ummm... (I think I know what it is.)
I'm worried I might break.
♪I feel like I'm going to break!♪
[Singing I can't breathe]
You did well! Miya did a great job!
It was so much fun!
You have to say what time it starts and
why I'm lying down here.
We went to the beauty saloon at 5 AM.
Went at 5 o'clock, got out at 8 and
came here at 9:30...
We've done the dry rehearsal and just ended it.
What time is it now?
It's 11:37 AM now.
We have a pre-recording around 4 PM... the wait is too long, so Miya is lying down to rest.
This happens when I sleep in the waiting room!
Now!
Miya's feet
Do you know why it's like this?
- If you sleep with them on...
- Oh, they come out!
So, if they come out, my toes get cold.
Yes, uh... This was Miya!
This was the interview! I'm going.
After that...
Now!
Soso!
Socks pretending to be gloves
[Embarrassed Soso]
- We're at Music Bank's waiting room...
- That's right!
Soso came back to Korea...
It's our first Music Bank since our
comeback, how is it?
Please tell me your impressions!
Nice to meet you... and...
[Long face came out because the
impression was short]
- What?!
- Speak more!
Yes, we are talking now!
Why are you in such a hurry? Person!
I'm Korean...
I think I'm going to see Seokyoung next time!
Seoryoung unnie!
Oh, hello!
Seoryoung unnie today is the first
Music Bank performance!
- Tell us how it feels.
- Uh... Music Bank...
Yesterday, we performed on M Countdown. Music Bank welcomed us with a cozy atmosphere.
And I'm a little tired after coming a little early.
I'm getting dark circles and I need to get
some sleep because my face is swollen!
The biggest feature of Music Bank!
Dry rehearsal and bedtime, then camera rehearsal.
- I'm thinking about what to do now.
- Is it hard?
I'll work and sleep right after!
Fighting!
Now! The next one is!
She's the cutest and prettiest girl in
the world and...
She has changed her hair a little.
Our cutie!
Let's go see Lena! Lena, the youngest!
Lena! Today is Music Bank's first
performance, how is it?
Thank you!
So... next one!
[MC Dung playing hard to get]
I'm hurt!
No! I'm fine!
I've just been rehearsing...
Q. How do you feel about the first performance of Music Bank?
Music Bank rehearsals are always fun!
I can't tell why...
I don't know if it's because it's been a while.
Yesterday's MCountdown recording was so much fun.
Today's rehearsal was also fun, and I'm really looking
forward to the main stage!
Are you confident that you'll do a good job?
Of course! I'm monitoring right now...
I rehearsed earlier.
After that!
The last one is finally here!
She's here, folks!
Are you looking forward to it, everyone?
[Disappointed because no one answered]
No one is answering...?
No one was expecting it...
Folks, are you looking forward to it?
[The good manager answers]
Yes, that's the state of today's interview...
Last in order!
The best in the world... the cutest...
she's the prettiest and she's introducing
the members.
There are people who say, "this person
is crazy..."
Now!
Minju! Hello!
Yes, I'm going to interview Minju today.
Miss Minju!
Can you tell me about your first stage?
Oh, I'm looking forward to the first broadcast!
Uh... I'm so excited to go up on stage!
Ah, thank you, miss Minju!
Please work hard today! Fighting!
Then the interview ends here.
Bye!
[Interview done!]
Well, today is Music Bank's first stage!
Fighting!
Girls in the Park!
1, 2, 3, fighting!
30/05/21 "Like it Hot" at Inkigayo
[Hi, groos!]
Where are we?
This is Inkigayo!
30/05/21 "Like it Hot" at Inkigayo
Where are we?
This is Inkigayo!
I did a ponytail today.
Here's a cute invisible ribbon holding it.
Today we're going to rehearse in our outfits!
Fighting!
Bye!
Hi!
Today, we are preparing for Inkigayo on Sunday!
Exactly.
Today is the pre-recording!
This way we are preparing fast!
- I got a notice that there is a fancam today.
- That's right!
I am very nervous.
- You'll be fine even though you're nervous?
- Yes, I will.
- For today's concept, we have shiny extensions!
- Greet the camera, Miya unnie!
- You'll be fine even though you're nervous?
- Yes, I will.
- For today's concept, we have shiny extensions!
- Greet the camera, Miya unnie!
Hello, this is Miya!
My hair...
[Miya getting interrupted]
Oh, I didn't know you were in the middle
of an interview!
Hi!
We're at Inkigayo today!
First Inkigayo this comeback!
The stage is so pretty and...
The stage is pretty and the members are prettier.
Thanks!
Actually, I really wanted to compliment you.
I know (x3)
[You knew it! As expected!]
- I... I know how you feel!
- Oh, really?
In fact, aren't we going to be ending fairies today?
- That's right!
- We're doing the ending too!
- The point for the ending fairy is us!
- Lena wouldn't have done it without our hands.
[01's are the best!]
Today was the last music show of the first week.
First of all, it's the first week, and it's been too long since we've
had a music show.
I think it was a little... very difficult.
Still... I think there's
something a little awkward about it.
So, starting next week, I'll be a little closer (with the camera).
We'll come back prettier!
Uh, I was very worried... because it's been so long.
Also, the practice room and the stage are different.
What if you can't find the camera?
If you're nervous on stage, you might laugh.
Of course, I'm practicing to prevent that.
I've worried a lot about it.
We've had our first week with a very nervous mind.
I got used to it quickly because it's our 5th mini album.
I think we'll be able to show you a better performance!
How is "Like it Hot", everyone?
That's right! I like it, too!
Bye!
Is the first week already gone?
It's a little sad the time we have left is getting smaller and smaller because I want to show you more.
It's been a while since we've been on this show.
I don't want to go in!
I want to look prettier to Groo.
You're going to watch the performance, right?
You're going to watch, right?
Please watch the rest of the broadcasts.
Bye!
Groos, hi!
I'm getting fixed and then going to the practice room.
We haven't been here in a very long time!
But a lot of people were waiting for us.
I was so touched.
Many people looked forward to it and
gave me good compliments.
So we want to do better for the rest
of the promotions.
I have a strong desire to do better!
I worked hard on today's broadcast.
I hope you enjoy watching it!
Fighting!
We come here every time we comeback!
4th time?
I feel I can relax more on stage now.
We'll be back next week with the members.
I believe you'll be able to see various gestures!
We had a fun stage today! Please enjoy it!
You know I watch you when you whisper
"Like it Hot" at the beginning?
- Miya unnie is acting cool.
- I whispered lightly today.
Did you? Did you?
I'll do this move next week. I look forward to it!
Where are we now? This is...
This is Inkigayo!
Today we had the first "Like it Hot"
performance of Inkigayo.
I didn't think about the ending, so I went up on
stage, and before the recording.
You said I was the ending fairy today, but I was like
'I'm not doing the same thing as everyone?' and then...
What? Do I have to do something?
"I'm sure you'll do something cute" you guys said.
So I got a little embarassed.
But Soso unnie and Minju unnie helped me.
So, check out what I've done in the broadcast!
Again... I liked it a lot.
The producers of Inkigayo did a great job.
I did it with confidence!
It's our first time doing it, so we're going to show you more stages in the future with more confidence.
Bye!