Everyone, there was something
I said I was preparing for in secret~
Here it is!
This is my first acting challenge!
Anne's first acting challenge!
[Anne working hard even in hot weather]
Today I filmed my first web drama "Half Fifty".
Yesterday I couldn't sleep and was very nervous,
but it looks like it ended well.
I'll prepare well for tomorrow too.
I will try to shoot as well as today~
Please support "Half Fifty" a lot!
[Anne waiting for the last filming.]
Today is the last shooting day!
That's really unfortunate...
Now it's over...
I think it's the beginning,
I believe everything seems like that.
When you're getting used to it,
then it ends like this.
Very unfortunate.
But I work hard until the end of the day~
This time I'll shoot a fun scene.
[Getting ready to shoot again!]
It's a shooting we have to film inside for a bit.
Receiving a request from a friend...
It's a scene like that.
I'm done for today.
How unfortunate...
[Feeling sorry...]
I need to increase the tension now~
I think I can take this scene~
Spotting a celebrity.
"This is my first time seeing a celebrity!"
[Excited!]
Can I take a picture?
Uh?! Are you a comedian?
Ah, what do I do! ㅠㅠ
I feel something awkward here.
I think this should really be a fuss...
[Preparing to shoot the scene we practiced~]
Contrary to worries, acting spontaneously succeeds!
Oh yes, this was my first acting challenge.
'Half Fifty' filming is over.
At first, it was like "what should I do?"
I couldn't sleep at night
and kept memorizing the lines.
I asked the members: "Is this okay?"
Saying "which is better?"
I was really worried while I prepared for this.
Fortunately, there is something to learn while doing this.
I wasn't as anxious as I thought
and it was such a great time.
For me, learning in the field
is much better than acting alone
and it was really special.
It was such a precious time for me,
I learned a lot of good things here
and if a good opportunity like this comes
I'll be working hard
to show you something good.
Please support "Half Fifty" a lot, everyone~
It will be really fun! If you don't see it, you'll regret it~
Please support "Half Fifty" a lot~
Bye bye~!
[GWSN - Girls in the Park Translations
Subtitles by archie]