GWSN - Girls in the Park Translations
Shall I try it?
So cute!
MIYA'S KOREAN LIFE
GWSN - Girls in the Park Translations
Subs by archie
I've made it!
I've arrived at the Dongmyo Market.
Now I'll find something that fits me!
Wow, this is fun~
It's already fun.
It's like a festival!
Festival!
I have to find pretty stuff.
This one is also used.
I bought it in Japan...
in a vintage shop? I bought it there.
This was 2,000 Yen...
Is it cheap?
20,000 Won in Korean currency!
20,000 won coat.
(Manager) It's all piled up there.
Wow, this is hard to do~
This is harder than I thought...
Shall I try it on?
So cute!
Before the warmer seasons, it's cold without a jacket,
and it is hot if it is very thick.
I want to buy a vest as well!
I don't wear vests because I don't have one...
so I want one to try it.
If it goes badly,
I might look like a fisherman!
It is hard to choose well.
I like this simple sweatshirt.
It's okay.
Is this okay?
Just put this with denim pants and done!
I want to do that.
With ripped ones.
There are a lot of cute things... what should I do?
I can't choose.
(Next store! Go!)
Isn't it cool?
Can you see it?
What do you think?
Like this.
Whoever sees this knows it's Miya's style~
Isn't it cute? The shirt is so cute~
This is a little scary because of the red coat,...
but not if it's a cute piece...
Wow~ cute!
Doesn't it look cool?
(Applause for Miya's style)
Wow, cool!
It's dressing well today!
I like this!
How about it?
I like it~
Postpone it?
This is almost a fix! haha
Wow~ I like it here.
I saw a few places...
wasn't it nice?
So good~
There are a few things I liked.
I'm looking at it a little different,
and I'm going to buy here again.
There are more styles that suit me than I thought...
so I really like it.
Obviously Miya's style!
There's not only clothes here,
but also other things.
It's fun.
I think I'll come here everyday to buy clothes!
It's totally nice~ And it's better than I thought.
It was not that expensive, it was cheap!
10,000 won, 20,000 won...
Not much more than that...
I like it~
I'll try this hat...
Ah, it's small?
It's small...