GWSN - Girls in the Park Translations
Isn't it okay to use it like this?
Isn't it pretty?
MIYA'S LIFE IN KOREA EP. 8
GWSN - Girls in the Park Translations
Subtitles by archie
Here!
I found another store... I'll go in!
This style is also pretty.
Isn't this pretty?
The one-piece we saw earlier are cute, but there are so many here too.
There is also this.
How do you wear this?
Aren't my legs too short?
Look at the legs!
30,000 won!
I'll wear it.
A casual vibe...?
It doesn't even feel like hip-hop.
How is it? It's cute.
Is there anything that suits you?
(Manager 2) There's a shirt in the front that suits you.
A cute image!
Next!
How about this?
Doesn't go well with these pants,
but this shirt pops up...
It's simple...
The material is good.
I feel good when I wear it.
This is the shirt~
What i thought was...
I'll wear a hoodie and a tie.
Wouldn't it be cool with a tie?
Isn't this pretty? An accessory like a tie.
Even if it's a scarf.
Oh, this is pretty...
First of all, I like this style more than I thought.
I don't wear a lot of bright colors,
so this new feeling is fine.
I want to wear a tie over this shirt...
If there is anything here, it's even cuter...
It's a different story.
Should I make ties a new "Miya item"?
What do you think?
The tie is cute...
Should I try the sweater? I'll wear it again!
If you all like this, this is it!
Anything like a hat?
Isn't it okay to use it like this?
Isn't it pretty?
I really liked this combination!
This pale yellow with pink!
The decision is... I will go with this!
I could wear it not only like this...
but I can wear only this.
So when I think about it...
the sweater is more versatile.
I'll take it!
Isn't this cute?
Isn't it?
It's just... cute.
It's cute, and...
there's a 'Did Miya design it?' vibe to it.
I'm having a hard time now.
I used all my energy there!
But wasn't the last place nice?!
This is cool... is this (just) 10,000 won?!
Is it okay?
(Decided to buy it!)
Thank you!
Shall we go this way?
[To take a taxi.]
I'm back!
Today, I went to the Dongmyo flea Market.
Uh... honestly...
it was fun!
Next time I'll look for more things my style.
Please look forward to this Miya's vlog!
Today was very fun.
Everyone, please go!
Dongmyo Market~ It's really fun!
It's so fun!
Ah.. I spent more time than I expected...
so I slept a lot in the taxi.
Please support my future vlogs!
That’s it for today~
Bye!
I just want to try it on!
Just try it on!
So cute!
Doesn't it look good?
Really cute!