Dip here and eat.
(Already) Delicious!
[On the ceiling of the mouth] It's stuck, it's stuck!
Miya's life in Korea Wish List
Hello, everyone~
This is pretty.
Pretty?
I've prepared for this.
Today...
I'm going to the market.
So...
I'm going to dress well to go to the market because
I'm going for the first time
Many things to look forward to!
First of all,
The weather is nice today,
so I have to pick clothes in here.
It's the "Miya Area"~
Jacket, I have to choose a jacket.
Today~
because I'm wearing black underneath,
shall I use this?
Red color~
Red coat~
Wearing this red coat!
Let's go to a special market~
Today's fashion.
All black inside!
Outstanding red~
The mask is also black~
Let’s go!
It's a little late, hehe.
Feels like the weather today
is neither good nor bad?
(Manager) Miya-san~
Yeah!
Where are you going today?
(Miya) Today...
To the market!
A special market!
Dong~myo?
(Manager) The flea market~
Flea mar-?
The flea market!
I'm going to buy clothes~~~
Clothes, clothes, clothes, clothes, clothes~
Hi!
Uh... I've arrived at the market.
But before going to the Dongmyo flea market,
I came here to see the Gwangjang Market~
I came to the Gwangjang Market first.
So, I'll go in for the first time!
Wow~ Looks good~
All look good~
Huh! Dumplings, dumplings!
Isn't it amazing?
Yes!
It's awesome~
In Japan there aren't many places like this.
It's the first time I see something like this.
This huge!
It feels like abroad! Overseas!
(Manager) For Miya this feels like overseas.
Ah, that's right! For me, this is overseas.
(Manager) You have to eat the beandae cake too~
(Excited woman)
[Food was distributed in separate plates.]
(Miya) Wow! It's moving!
It's moving~!
It is moving!
(So good~)
I should eat~
(Manager) Pop the yolk!
(Manager 2) This, this (you can mix it!)
This? Mix it (with the meat)?
Yes!
Can it be mixed?
(Shake It~ Shake It~)
There is radish!
I'm not good at mixing.
(Manager 2) So, this pear,
you eat this together.
(Miya) With pear~
(Manager) And meat~
Put it on a spoon and eat it~
Like this?
Yeah~ (That's right!)
Oh, it's delicious~
(Manager 2) Try the live octopus as well.
Ah, is it a bit big?
Isn't it a bit big?
Ah, it's okay~
Dip here and eat.
(Already) delicious!
It's stuck, it's stuck!
It's stuck!
On the ceiling of the mouth.
Delicious~
[Thumbs up]
Ah, it hurts, hurts!
It hurts, it hurts!
(Manager 2) This is the beandae cake!
(Manager) Kimchi pancakes...?
[The managers wanted to show the taste of Korean food!]
[V]
(Manager 2) Hot, hot!
Is it good?
This is banquet noodles (janchiguksu)!
Have you tried?
Is there blanquet in there?
It's called banquet noodles because they ate it on festive days!
Ah~! Hehe
In the old days, at weddings and such occasions...
Koreans ate banquet noodles.
There is also a meaning of making a decision when eating noodles.
Is it tasty?
That's the expression of truth~
(Manager 2) Which of these have you eaten before?
Beandae cake and wookhoe bibimbap!
Have you tried the banquet noodles before?
(Have I tried eating it...?)
Is it my first time for the banquet noodles?
(Manager 2) It looks a little like "udon".
Ah, it's similar, yeah!
One pretzel.
Thank you~!