77 years old....
GWSN - Girls in the Park Translations
Did you believe it?
Yeah!
Were you really surprised?
77 years old.
And then I said...
"What are you doing!"...
[The boys are already relaxed]
One last greeting
We'll greet you first.
1, 2, 3!
[A group greeting that is not that good...]
[The seniors are good together...]
We will also greet you!
Hi! We are Girls in the Park! Thank you!
[A performance so dreamy and unique!]
[Girls in the Park]
It's our CD...
The album is out...
Thank you!
Thanks in advance.
Nucksal senior...! No, wait...
I'm meeting a junior today, so...!
I came with the same hair!
Nucksal style!
Oh, maybe...
Haven't you been doing this before...?
It's my first time with a moving camera...
Can I get some advice?
I believed it was important looking at the camera.
In the old days it was fashionable to follow the camera.
Nowadays... You have to look a little uninterested too?
If it's my part I don't pierce through the camera, it's like...
"You're shooting me, but I won't see you!"
An unfocused vibe, in your eyes?
I have another question
The active camera has a red light on.
Even looking away I can see the red light.
But to turn and look right away... isn't that a bit weird?
If I'm looking here... I do it like...
- Following the beat!
- Slightly upturned... like this!
So you do it like this?
Jay Fox (Park Jaebom)
Brother, can you try it once?
Camera flash!
You want to know something...?
That's exactly it...
[That's... right?]
I feel so different.
And these days, the ending fairy...
is more than breathing heavily...
it needs a little more impact.
So that will increase the engagement.
That's how it gets on the thumbnail!
Will we...
Will we get hits?
I heard you're the youngest
That's right.
[Youngest & Leader]
These days... the Bite Heart...
Did you know that's trending?
- Bite...?
- Bite Heart!
[Demonstration team]
If the youngest does that maybe
the fans will like it.
Don't do this, I could hit you if you do this!
So don't...
That's right!
What's wrong with it?...
How do you do it?
Ah, like this!
Oh, this is poo!
[This video does not contain implicit advertising]
[We're cheering for the masters of jinx, though!]
Did you rehearse this?!
You practiced this, didn't you?
We.... we didn't know...!
I've never met her!
You practiced this?
Write "Famous Burger" here!
Oh, your pronunciation looks good...
have you ever lived abroad?
A little bit.
We have an overseas member...
Hwang Dong-hyun (main vocalist)
He has lived in Canada for 30 years.
I feel more comfortable now...
Well, "how long is you there"? In california.
How long stay there?
But can you speak it for real?
I'm really curious.
Change back now, change!
Back to normal, back to normal!
Wait... When he speaks English he's suddenly like...
This is a habit...
And speaking Korean ﻿"Uh, everyone!"
Oh, I'm sweating...
[It kept pouring out...]
Mills...
Are you sweating right now?
I'm too nervous during greetings.
Too close?
I'm going to smell bad and I just...
I'm afraid my nose hair is sticking out now...
[GWSN is coming back to deliver a gift!]
- Now I'll just play Jay Park.
- He's tired!
Staff: You mentioned you were a junior member.
The only senior among us is Jaebum.
That's right...
Right...
In fact…
[We met Girls in the Park again!]
2, 3!
Hi! We are GWSN! Thank you!
You did it again right away!
Like this...
We want to give you our album.
Thank you so much!
Short haired fairy!
I will cherish it!
Thank you!
I will keep it forever.
Staff: Please give a word of thanks.
Jay Park!
What should I say?
You came this far because...
you debuted and worked really hard...
I don't think there's much to worry about if you keep it up.
Fighting!
[It was nice to meet you, GWSN!]
Oh, so natural...