GWSN - Girls in the Park Translations
[HANLIM HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATION INTERVIEW]
Hello! I'm Girls in the Park's Lena,
[Filmed in compliance with the COVID-19 prevention regulations.]
practical music student at Hanlim Arts School.
Q. How was the shooting for your graduation book?
A little awkward, but I smiled at the picture...
because my friends were being funny.
Q. Could you show the pose you did?
I think I did it like this ^-^
Q. What would you like to eat on graduation day?
I want to eat my mother's food.
Q. What photo hashtags are you using during the ceremony?
#I'm_already_graduating
#I'm_already_graduating #Friends_how_are_you?
#I'm_already_graduating #Friends_how_are_you? #I'll_come_back_to_eat pizza_bread
Q. Please, talk about your activities last year.
I was busy promoting our 4th mini album...
with "BAZOOKA" as the title song.
Q. Any regretable or proud moments during the activities?
It's pity that I couldn't see the fans, but...
I was proud making good songs with the members.
Q. What do you want to do when you turn 20?
I want to go on a trip with my friends.
Q. Any stories about Hanlim's practical music entrance exam?
There is no special story, but...
I was a trainee when I took the exam...
and debuted after entering the school.
Q. Do you have any tips for the practical exam?
If you practice hard,
won't you show confidence instead of fear?
Q. Could you sing a song that you sang during the entrance exam?
I sang "Unfaithful" by Rihanna.
I'm from the practical music department, so...
Q. Do you have any memorable moments while attending Hanlim?
I remember that my friends gathered during breaks...
and sang songs, played the piano and the guitar.
I haven't been to any restaurants around school, but...
the pizza bread at school was really good.
Q. Favorite snack?
Chocolate?
Q. What song concept would you want to try in the future?
I want to sing a song that everyone can enjoy
while communicating with the audience.
When I'm active I don't have time to practice.
Q. How do you use your leisure time to heal?
I don't have time to learn a song if I want to...
so I try to practice a lot during my breaks.
I think I had a great with my friends in Hanlim.
Q. Please, talk about your graduation.
I'm sorry that I have already graduated.
Let's all meet again in good shape and in a safe way.
Gong: Study and....
Q. Can you make a poem with "Gongwon Sonyeo"? [Girls in the Park]
Won: play hard and...
So: make a wish...
Yeo: Everyone!
I believe you asked a lot of interesting questions,
Q. Last words for the interview, please!
so I had a lot of fun in this interview.