GWSN - Girls in the Park Translations
2, 3!  Waiting for you!
Hello!  We are Girls in the Park!
Yes, we got together wearing pretty stage outfits for this!
- Why are we here today, everyone?
- Today... we are going to do a MV reaction!
This is the first time we are going to watch it together!
First time!  I'm going to start it!
(Watching on a monitor connected to the laptop)
- Wow! Isn't this our outfit?
- It was similar!
Wow!!
Hey, Soso, your hair is pretty!
Is it not?
- Your faces are glowing, girls!
- The lighting was strong!
Lena, is your hair short?
It was really purple at that time!
All our hairs looked good.
The colors are very bright.
- The atmosphere here is really eerie.
- That's right!
- Doesn't it feel like a dream?
- True!
Yeah, a real dream.
I was there when they were filming.
Minju watched from the back.
This was the first scene!
Fishlens shot!
So I felt a bit awkward, because it
was my first scene in a while.
It's very lively.
I can't stop coughing when I do that.
Ah, cute!
My bangs are all split!
So pretty!
- Wow! The car scene now!
- We're next!
I'm really driving!
- I know!
- I know, you did it like this!
- Anne, wasn't the car hot?
- Yeah, but just a little warm!
Glad to hear that!
-Oh?! It was very windy at that time.
-Right!
- Wait a minute, isn't this like Puzzle Moon?
- It's a connection?
But the members have changed!
Minju is like "tak tak"! And I'm like "uh..."
Lena was there when I was walking
and it was so funny!
- Oh, this was fun!
- True!
That camera was really close (?),
but we sang the whole song!
That was great!
I'm excited!
When we filmed that, they said we
were doing great!
I was so touched!
You can see it's cold because of the
fog outside, right?
- It was so cold here!
- But it was less cold than Bazooka's shooting!
We were kids in "Bazooka!"
It looks indoors, but it was outdoors.
- That's computer graphics behind me.
- That's right. So good!
I was worried doing that because I can't
improvise well!
So beautiful!
It's got a good vibe.
- Why didn't I know about this?
- Now you know!
It's Minju!!!
That's a very chic look.
- Seokyoung is so cute!
- Seokyoung is excited!
Oh, look at the formation.
Excited!
I believe it's great there are a lot of scenes
like this.
It's like a family photo, gathered
Yes!
It looks like we entered a dream when
it started...
and woke up when it ended.
It's the feeling of entering a dream and then waking up.
It's a MV that connects the stories so far,
and this feels like starting over again!
So, after a story like this... if I were
Groo I would be like...
"What's happening next? I believe it
will be like this!"
Bazooka was like a bridge between
our albums.
"Bazooka!" has its own feeling, and Like it Hot follows
Puzzle Moon, Pinky Star (RUN) and Red-Sun (021).
- It seems to be an extension, so I believe it means something.
- True!
And everyone came out pretty!
Whose MV is that?
It's ours!
[Anne was deceived again...]
I was like this!
[Shhh, everyone!]
You were doing it? You're so mean.
- I didn't do it either!
- Oh really?
We're not fools anymore!
I... I... (I didn't see...)
- We're not stupid anymore!
- Anne is a fool!
Anne is a fool!
No, I like Soso so much!
Cute!
- But, to be honest, we're the main characters.
- That's right!
By the time this video is out, there must
have already been a lot of videos of us performing.
I think we were able to see our choreography
and scenes better.
It's been a while since we've done this,
and we look so pretty.
We've done a lot of styling that we
haven't done before.
So I think Groo will like it, right?
I especially liked the half-and-half jacket.
- I love it! It was better than I thought.
- This is the first time we tried clothes like this.
But to be honest, I was a little worried.
We wanted to show you two sides of us.
I was worried some of you wouldn't like it.
- Fortunately, thank you for liking it, everyone!
- Yes!
- Please watch our MV a lot!
- Please watch it a lot!
There are many things in the MV that
you can't see on stage!
Please also watch the MV a lot!
I hope you also react to it and watch it a lot.
We'll say goodbye!
Until now, 2, 3!  Waiting for you!
This was Girls in the Park!  Thank you!