GWSN - Girls in the Park Translations
2, 3!  Waiting for you!
Hi! We are Girls in the Park!﻿
What do you guys see here?
What is this?
Yeah, this time...
We've made a comeback with our 5th mini-album
"The Other Side of the Moon"!
So, we've brought our album!
Really pretty!
Before we open, the other side of the moon is our concept,
So the moon shape is cut in half, everyone!
We wanted to capture this, folks!
I'll open it first, everyone!
First of all, hold your emotions, everyone!
just a little...
That's how I'll do it!
Wow, the CD!
Really pretty!
The CD is really something very exotic.
Miya unnie designed this too!
Really?
You'll hear about how she felt about designing this later!
Now, as soon as I see this I feel like
it's a little bit like the surface of the moon.
Doesn't it feel a little more bizarre?
It feels like a reflection!
[Gathering together to browse the album]
As soon as we open it, the songs included are shown.
From the first to the sixth track.
Let's see what comes next!
Kim Miya!
Miya unnie's image is a little different from ours.
So I always thought it would be nice...
to raise her coolness
This time, she cut off the bangs,
and then gave her pointy eyebrows...
as soon as I saw it I was like, "Oh, very pretty!"
I was like this
Miya unnie pages are over,
Next!
Seoryeong
Seoryoung, you have black hair this time!
Yeah! I always use bright colors.
Right.
This time I tried black hair.
The fans are very supportive...
and the members also like it, so I think it's very good.
I'm seeing your hair black for the first time.
My hair is originally brown.
I'm trying black hair for the first time ever!
But it suits you well
Like you've grown your original hair.
Yes, I like it!
Unnie, after you dyed your hair
you looked in the mirror and said: "Oh, is this okay?"
- Did you?
- Me?
Unnie, you did it! You were next to me!
I saw it!
Really?
- Wasn't it "it's better than I thought?"
- Ah, right. That's it!
You came out like a doll!
Beautiful!
Personally, I was a bit disappointed.
I feel like the feeling has to be clear
something like a bright feeling.
I feel like the picture didn't show much.
You can show it a lot on stage!
Please watch the stages a lot, everyone!
Who is next?
To be honest, I have a feeling!
The prettiest person will show up!
I have that kind of intuition!
Wasn't I right?!
The prettiest person has come out, everyone!
- What will you do? Whoever comes after her!
- Introduce yourself!
This person right here is called Minju...
How about this hair bleaching?
I like this color.
I heard that bleaching doesn't hurt as much as I thought!
I bleached my hair 3 or 4 times
and it didn't hurt at all!
So I have a very strong scalp.
Next one...
At this point, If you've seen our videos...
and the Girls in the Park thumbnails,
it gets predictable!
I'm feeling this next one has hair bangs...
Feeling like something changed this time...?
A feeling she has a 3 layered hair?
I'm sensing a princess.
I'll do it... Everyone! Please tell me if it's right!
That's right!
It's Lena!
I'm seeing it for the first time now!
Again...
The member with the biggest change is probably Lena.
Because...
We haven't dyed our hair or done anything
like that since our debut.
For the first time we've bleached our hairs
and Lena also had a "hime cut".
She's had a lot of changes.
So, after Lena made these changes,
I feel like she has matured a little more.
Lena's new style is very unique...
So, when we were filming the music video the other day,
I just saw Lena at the set with the background
She looked like something out of a game or a cartoon...
Or something like that...
Something from another world...
A goddess, or something like that...
Everyone, how many times did Seoryoung
say "something"?
Leave it in the comments! I appreciate it.
Yeah, count how many times I say "something"
Leave it in a comment and I'll give you a gift!
My love!
I will introduce the next member!
I think I know who the next member is!
Anne's unnie!
Unnie was next to me during the individual shooting.
She looked just like a doll.
This ribbon is so well done!
And she has a hair bun too...
It seems it can't get cuter that that.
It seems to me Anne is cuter than
during "Bazooka" promotions.
After that, we will introduce the other members.
Next one!
Seokyoung unnie!
Seokyeong unnie changed a lot this time too!
I think short hair suits her so well...
Not even joking, why hasn't she
done it all this time?
As soon as I saw her short hair I said
"Unnie, you're VERY pretty!"
I just realized she looks so good with short hair.
That's right!
Rather, it feels more awkward with long hair now...
Yeah, right!
Lastly...
Soso!
I'm back!﻿
Soso also cut her bangs for the first time!
Yes!  And I cut the hair length a lot too.
As we always said, Soso should cut her bangs!
This time, it hit me! It's really cool!
I like it a lot.
We still have a lot to show you in the album.
There are a lot of photos with so many
different and pretty faces.
Everyone, please take a close look all the
way to the back.
And everyone, we've finished introducing the album,
but it's not over yet!
Ah, that's right!
When you buy the album other things come with it.
Isn't there always items in GWSN's albums?
You haven't seen the components yet.
Our items will be introduced by the next team.
Let's see!
Hello! We are following the previous team
This is the beautiful trio who will
introduce the album gifts.
What shall we see first?
First of all, our album is right in front of us.
After that, 2 photo cards and
2 bookmarks and
drawn and written by ourselves... stickers!
Then there's 2 posters!
Then, shall we start by looking at the insides?
"PhoCa"!
Is it ok?
Alright, let's show the photo cards!
Before the photos, let's show the album properly.
The album cover!
Follow me!
So pretty!
Who designed it?
Wow! Who designed it?
Can you see me?﻿
We've released 4 albums so far...
Yeah!
But all of them were squared!
Squared!
Yeah, that's it.
But this time it's a little bit different
Didn't the image change too?
That's right...
Uh, who designed it?
I heard it was a genius cat!
-Oh, really?
-Yes!
It was me!
- Ok.
- It's pretty!
But I also brought the original picture this time!
This is the canvas that I originally painted.
This is on the album...
This is how it happened.
Miya unnie's skills get better as they go on!
But why did I pick this style?
Why did I do something like this...
Please explain!
First of all, I didn't paint it like this.
There is a technique called Pouring Art.
There is a way to paint, pouring it like this...
And this is how the dye is spread.
So, if you do this, it will come out naturally.
But if you ask someone to do it the same way, they can't.
That's right!
So, in that sense...
Our album is unique in the world and
[So cool!]
It has such a special meaning!
Oh, what a genius!
An album like no other!
It means so much...
- It has that meaning.
- Well, done Miya.
Not even the artist can reproduce!
Have you tried it with other colors?
Different colors...
- Maybe somewhere else?
- It's somewhere else?
- On our CD...
- That's how it came out!
The CD is the other picture you mentioned, right?
Oh! Cute!
So cute...
Isn't it cute?
- Isn't it?
- Really pretty!
Where is the top and the bottom?
Everyone who sees it feels differently.
It's a real work of art, unnie.
The CD is written like this.
Looking at this picture now, it looks like this
The direction was also thought of.
Once you see it like this, this is the best direction.
But it can also be on the left and at the bottom.
I've been thinking a lot about whether it's underneath.
Then I like the versions on the cover and on
the CD the most.
Thank you!
Now, everyone, you can call it the
flower of the album!
Let's introduce you to the photo cards.
There are two types of photo cards.
One has a signature and a message
written on the back.
One is just a regular photo card.
This is Anne!
We haven't seen all the members yet.
I don't know how it came out
- Let's see something else!
- So I have a photo card like this one,
I hope you all get your favorite photo!
- And what do you want to see next?
- The two bookmarks!
This was designed...
Isn't it pretty?
- This one is different!
- Oh, right!
It matched this part.
Genius! genius!
Our Miya is a genius!
So what about this bookmark?
There will be one in two chances, randomly!
But here's the point, folks!
If you look at the bottom of this, you can see a small signature of Miyauchi Haruka.
That's right! Actually, I worked hard this time
Rather than Miya from GWSN,
I thought it was nice to sign as Miya the designer.
I signed the M. Haruka's autograph!
Unnie's signature!
That's right! I've done the signature!
And now...
Sticker!
Now let's show you what's left!
Oh, I like it.
Then, let's try rock, paper, scissors!
Whoever wins starts.
Alright!
Go on, unnie.
- Isn't it cool?!
- Very nice!
If I were Groo, I would have this on the wall
I'd put it beside the bed.
And I'd sleep like this.
Pretty...
I'd say hello every day before bed
and after getting up.
So that I can meet you even in my dreams
Right!
- Pinned by the bedside!
I'll also flip it now!
How is it?
I'm scared, I'm scared!
Who is this?!
Who is it?!
- Aren't the members so pretty?
- So beautiful...
These were...
This cafe where the music video and photoshooting
were filmed has a lot of themes.
So like we did...
you can also take pictures with various concepts!
We recommend you to visit it.
Please go there and do the same poses.
- "Park" spot!
- 7 people needed!
Good!
Looking for Groo to go with me!
There is more things in the album, isn't there?
[I almost forgot!]
Everyone, I'm going to show the most important thing.
We're giving it to fans who bought it on pre-order.
Now, there are 10 two cuts pictures...
We took pictures like that.
There are Day and Night versions of it.
Because there are 10 pieces by 7 people.
It's a total of 70 pieces!
We are gifting it only to those who have pre-ordered.
Only the Groos who get it will know
how they look like.
Now, this is how we end the introduction
of the album gifts.
Don't you think there's something really
good about this album?
- There's a lot...
- And it's not very common.
This one was actually designed by unnie herself.
Also, this is a picture that she can't
possibly draw again.
We also drew and wrote the letters ourselves.
I believe these are really meaningful items.
It's been a while since our group
released an album...
After 1 year!
We've changed not just our visuals this last year, but...
the album, posters, concepts, and even songs...
it's an album that will show you a new look.
From the design to the lyrics,
a lot of the members participated.
I hope that many people will love it and
we will work hard so that this
promotion can be done safely!
Fighting!
Girls in the Park Fighting!
Then, let's say goodbye.
Until then,
2, 3! Waiting for you! We are GWSN! Thank you!