GWSN - Girls in the Park Translations
Hello~ Everyone!
Do you know why I'm here today, everyone?
Yes, that's right!
Today I came to shoot for Schoolooks!
Last time I did a winter outfit shooting,
and today I came to shoot in summer clothes!
I'm scheduled to shoot first.
I'll work hard for this one too!
Bye!
[GWSN - Girls in the Park Translations
Subtitles by archie]
So, hello everyone!
Today I'll do a snack review...
[﻿Lena's snack review time.]
I have already finished this.
These potato chips are popular...
When I was in middle school...
I remember buying it with my friends.
Now, wasabi beans.
It's not spicy at all!
It hits your nose, but it's not that spicy.
And the reason for doing this today!
When I heard that Chocopie has a banana flavor,
I brought one!
This is banana coating!
But then, is it not chocolate?
If not, it's not Chocopie!
[Lena disappointed because there's no chocolate.]
I thought banana was covering the chocolate bread.
Personally, I don’t like banana taste very much...
so, that's not my style.
[Fast attitude change mode.]
I'll be back next time!
Unnie Minju, hi!
To: Minju
Do you have any idea why I turned on the camera?
Minju said that on the day of filming...
I shouldn't eat salty food because...
yesterday you gave me a Shinshindang.
But, there are so many delicious things here, unnie!
Look, can you see it?
I've never seen anything like this in my life!
So, the advice you gave me...
I don’t think I’ll be able to keep it..
so I did this apology video letter!
I love you!
[Taking polaroids for an event.]
How can I give Groos all 10 different pictures?
[Changing into the last summer outfit. Go!]
This is the end of the Schoolooks shooting!
The last outfit shooting is over!
I hope the situation improves quickly so that...
our students can enjoy school in pretty uniforms.
Fighting~