GWSN - Girls in the Park Translations
Hello, everyone!
Today is a fashion filming day.
Now I'm going to get pretty!
The makeup is over!
We've made it thicker.
Now I'm getting my hair done~
Done!
Feels different because it was done in the hair salon.
Well, now!
I'm going to the studio!
Let's do a shooting!
Let's go~!
Arriving at the studio!
The weather is nice today...
But... I have to go inside.
Let's go~!
Almost there!
Here it is!
I'll go inside.
Ready, set, go!
[Look here too, please!]
How is it?
[MAD BOSS Mode On]
Miya kills people with a punch.
[It's more cute than scary!]
These are like clothes that you use in
a photoshoot in a very nice place!
Isn't it?
Can you imagine buying this at Dongmyo?
Today's concept is "﻿﻿retro"...
I went retro...!
I don't know~ It has a retro feel, but...
it's a little different because I'm wearing it?
It's hard to say...
Genre: Miya!
[﻿Can't strap it because of the coat!]
[The string is not loose!]
[Miya broke her reaction.]
I'm having fun shooting!
[Change to the next mood]
I changed my clothes!
Now I'm going to shoot the second concept.
"Natural" concept this time!
So I removed all my makeup.
Isn't it cute? Pink!
Let's go!
This time in a little bed!
"Miya room" concept.
It's like my room.
It's not my room, but it's like my room!
The room concept is pretty, right?
I'm going to shoot here.
(Now) Shall we shoot?
[Transformed into a fluffy cat.]
Q. Please explain the contents of the book!
Yes~ This book~
Oh, the title is~
I only know Damian!
You studied well too!
Do a paper on it.
[So excited!]
It's over... the shooting!
I tried this as a natural, cute and peaceful charm,
Q. What style is this outfit?
which is the opposite of the previous one.
This isn't a bit retro, but...
this is also Miya style!
Isn't it cute?
I also got it at the Dongmyo flea market!
I was like... "Miya in pink?"...
Q. Is pink Miya's color now?
It was better than I thought, so I used the opportunity!
How is it? Doesn't it go well?
Isn't it cute?
I don't usually like pink...
but I liked wearing it!
A few years ago I also tried pink hair~
And this time, I chose the clothes myself.
I went and bought it myself...
I also thought about hair and makeup.
Was that... ﻿"jacket"?
Even if the hair stylist has done it...
I've made suggestions.
This hair right now...
it's Miya's usual hair style.
My hair is getting longer these days...
"What do I do with my hair?"...
I always wonder.
So this time, isn't it really natural?
This is "natural" Miya.
It's a little different than before, right?
If it comes out differently, success!
This fashion film is showing...
how I usually wear.
All you Groos ou there...
If you want to be like Miya,
I would like you to wear like this.
[Zoot at Miya's style sample]
If you want to see more, I'll do it again!
It was fun!
Yeah! Success!