(It's so cool..)
GWSN - Girls in the Park Translations
(I can sport this!)
[Seokyoung's startup "Hatnim" challenge]
[Today Seokyoung will work as her own boss at "Hatnim's Film"]
[The magician stretch!]
[Brushing teeth in sync with the other side.]
GWSN - Girls in the Park Translations
Subtitles by archie
[Done washing up!]
The weather is so good today!
What do I wear today...
I'm worried.
(Miya) This is what the weather calls for!
This?
Sky blue?
Okay!﻿
(Miya) My style!
Ok!﻿
I'll wear the clothes recommended by my roommate.
Unnie, are you good at Japanese?
You are good at Japanese!
(Miya) Huh?! Hehehe
(Miya) I'm good at Japanese!
I'll introduce you later!
My roommate lent it to me.
I'm going to iron this.
Oh! What's this sound?
Is it a kettle?
Do you want to take a break?
(Miya) Sounds like it's eating ramen!
Unnie! I must have put in too much water!
(Miya) Oh! I guess you put in a lot!
(Miya) It's shooting out now!
You keep spitting it out?
Be careful, it's hot!
(I'm looking for) something gorgeous here...
(Miya) Something like the best!
Hey!
[Found a colorful vest!]
Looks good?
Bye!
She loves to sing and dance...
so she's doing that!
I'm in love with drawing these days!
So, it seems like...
It seems like I'm going to draw a picture!
(It's so cool..)
(I can sport this!)
Good! Good!
This is it!
I think it's okay.
[CEO Kim closes the door despite the camera.]
[Did you forget?]
[Still getting used to it.]
Do I tie it up?
Do I wear it loose?
Am I getting late now?
I have to arrive quickly within 30 minutes.
I can't...
I'm not sure.
Let's pack up first.
Diary,
pouch,
glasses,
wallet,
earphones to get me hyped up,
eyedrops,
mask! A must-have mask!
Since I'll have a meeting near the practice room,
I think I'll dance after dinner.
That's why I must bring practice clothes.
[Ready to go to work!]
Let's go to work!
I just said let's go to work...
It's really late!
Let's go!
Not this bag, though?
No, I have to go.
On the way to work!
The flowers are so pretty.
[The boss is blocked from entering?!]
Uh?
Uh? What are you talking about?
Whew! That's a relief!
[Arrived at work safely!]
Today's OOTD! [Outlook of the day]
[The room that only the boss can enjoy.]
I chose a colorful look!
In case this was bland...
I wore a colorful vest below.
And in order to look a little chic...
I'm wearing this tie!
[The CEO enters a private room.]
I have a meeting today.
The reason we have a meeting...
you'll find out in a little while.
I'm late now, so I'll go quickly.
Let's go quickly.
I'm going!
[Meeting! Go!]
[Silent conference room.]
[The boss is still unfamiliar with the employees.]
Now!
First of all, thank you for coming to the meeting!
We are a new company with only 2 months...
Even though, thank you so much for...
showing the commitment to work hard!
There aren't many employees, but...
Oh, I finally got my business card!
Here!
This is mine.
[The CEO does it humbly.]
Now, today!
Before the meeting...
I can't forgive this gloomy atmosphere!
All together!
Let's express our will.
If I'm in the dock, we're doing it all together!
Passion, passion, passion!
Passion!
Great! Good!
Very passionate!
Now everyone sit down!
Now, let’s proceed with the meeting.
Now, that’s it for today’s meeting.
I hope everyone will ﻿do well on the assignments!
Now...
Let’s go.
Don't doze off, work hard and...
It would be nice to finish work before lunch.
The meeting is over!
Go... You can go...
[Q1. Please introduce the company]
Oh yes, our company is 'Hatnim's Film'...
We take pictures, edit them and...
'Hatnim's Film' is a company that delivers memories.
[Q2. How is the atmosphere in the company?]
Wow! Our company atmosphere is good!
But a little...
All the staff here...
they have a quiet personality...?
[Q3. Do you have a good relationship with the staff?]
I think so.
There was no friction so far...
No friction and...
not much conversation either!
[Q4. How was your meeting today?]
First of all, the meeting was satisfactory!
I am satisfied~
[Q5. What slides did you show at the meeting?]
I tried to find out what's trending these days,
and I used the idea as an inspiration,
so I expressed it in a colorful and dynamic way.
Using something like my artistic sense?
I guess it was a little bit off with the employees.
How many days I...
It was made over a few days and nights,
so the reactions were slightly disappointing.
[Q6. Do you have any projects in the future?]
Our Hatnim's Film...
since we must not fall behind,
we believe we can make the Hallyu more appealing...
by adding value through our photos...
and by making goods and selling them.
I've finished the meeting now!
These days, handmade products are valuable.
So I'm going to make an employee ID myself.
Is this the average employee ID size?
[Seokyoung caught in a frame.]
I don’t have a picture right now...
so, I'll draw the logo of our company.
Is it good?